Guide to the School of Medicine, Yale University, Records of the Deputy Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Medicine, Yale University, records of the deputy dean
1917-2005
RU 745
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
20
(38 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, referrals, reports, reviews, photographs, and minutes documenting the activities and responsibilities of the deputy dean of the Yale School of Medicine. Included are the records of Arthur Ebbert, Jr. and Richard Belitsky as deputy dean.
Yale University. School of Medicine
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 27-B (YRG 27-B), Records of deputy, associate, and assistant deans of the Yale University School of Medicine.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, referrals, reports, reviews, photographs, and minutes documenting the activities and responsibilities of the deputy dean of the Yale School of Medicine. Included are the records of Arthur Ebbert, Jr. and Richard Belitsky as deputy dean.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Medical colleges; Medicine -- Study and teaching; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Ebbert, Arthur; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University. School of Medicine
- Records of the deputy dean Arthur Ebbert Jr., 1949-1987; Accession 1988-A-035
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023.
  - Alumni Bulletin, Yale Medicine
    - Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - File copies: complete set, 1953-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Yale Medicine (formerly "Alumni Bulletin"), 1966-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Yale Medicine Budget, 1966-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committees
    - Cancer Center
      - Advisory, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Executive, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Proposal, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 3 - 4)
    - Continuing Medical Education
      - Postgraduate Education Committee, 1962-1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Task Force #3 Connecticut Regional Medical Programs, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Dean's Committee on Veterans Administration Hospital, 1954-1984 (Box 2, Folder 7 - 9)
    - Dean's Committee on Veterans Administration Hospital, 1954-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10 - 12)
    - Graduate Medical Education, Task Force on, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Joint Committee of the Hospital of St. Raphael and Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Medical Development Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Professional Service Committee (formerly Clinical Practice), 1953-1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Sesquicentennial Committee, 1960-1972 (Box 3, Folder 17 - 18)
    - Yale-New Haven Medical Center
      - Advisory Committee (Committee on Educational Facilities), 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence
    - A - E (Box 5, Folder 1 - 6)
    - F - J, 1954-1987 (Box 7, Folder 19 - 22)
    - K - P, 1954-1987 (Box 8, Folder 23 - 30)
    - Q - Z, 1954-1987 (Box 9, Folder 31 - 37)
  - Courses, Seminars, Symposiums, Workshops
    - Advances Relating to Management of Carcinoma of the Rectum, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - American College of Cardiology, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Anatomy 201, 202, 1953-1972 (Box 10, Folder 3 - 4)
    - Cardiopulmonary Disease, Management of, 1958-1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Career Choice: Research project, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Chemotherapy of Neoplastic and Non-neoplastic Diseases, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Computer Sciences, Medical, 1969-1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Congenital Heart Disease in Infancy, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Connecticut Post Graduate Seminar in Psychiatry and Neurology, Inc., 1952-1973 (Box 10, Folder 10 - 13)
    - Contact Lens Fitting, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Coronary Training Program, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Crippled Children, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Curricular of Elective Courses, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Diabetes Mellitus, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Diagnostic Virology, 1962-1979 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Digestive Disorders, Medical Management of, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Endocrine Disease and Hormone Therapy, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Epidemiology, Clinical: Preventive Medicine 102, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1961-1966 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Gastrointestinal Disorders, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Head and Neck Cancer, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Heart Disease, Advances in Diagnosis and Management of, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Hematologic Problems, Management of, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Hematology and Oncology, Symposia on Recent Advances in, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Infectious Diseases: Problems of Clinical Diagnosis and Management, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Institute for the Special Care of Infants, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Iron Therapy, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Kidney Diseases, Diagnosis and Management, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Liver, Pancreas and Biliary Tract, Diagnosis and Management, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Malignant Diseases of Childhood, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Medical Education in the Community Hospital, 1960-1963 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Medicine 213-216, 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 36 - 39)
    - Microbiology 210, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Nasal Surgery, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Occupational Noise, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Ophthalmology, 1954-1961 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Pathology 200, 1955-1973 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Pathology of the Lung, 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Physical Medicine and Rheumatology, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Post Graduate Lecture Programs at Community Hospitals, 1951-1961 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Pregnancy Testing, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Public Health 118 (Medical Jurisprudence), 1954-1959 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Pulmonary Disease, Management of Chronic, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Radiology 302-307, 1952-1973 (Box 12, Folder 51 - 56)
    - Rheumatic Diseases, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - "Seminar on Curriculum Innovations in the Americas'', 1971 (Box 13, Folder 58 - 59)
    - Special Post Graduate Programs, Symposiums and Lectures, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Staphylococcal Infections and the Community Hospital (Waterbury Hospital), 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Student Advisory Council: general, 1964-1968 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Student Health Care Project, re: New London, Connecticut, 1968-1973 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Surgery (Box 13, Folder 64)
      - Surgery 110, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 65)
      - Surgery of the Larynx and Pharynx, 1965-1972 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Symposiums (miscellaneous), 1965-1970 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Trauma, Management of in the Community Hospital, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Yale Associates Program, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Liaison Committee on Medical Education (LCME) 1975
    - Organization Administration and Faculty (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Finances (Box 14)
    - Student Enrollment (Box 14)
    - Student Affairs (Box 14)
    - Plant (Box 14)
    - Library (Box 14)
    - Clinical Facilities (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Special Ambulatory (Box 14)
    - Clinical Facilities (Box 14)
    - Curriculum (Box 14)
    - Cytology (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Biochemistry (Box 14)
    - Pathology (Box 14)
    - Pharmacology (Box 14)
    - Physiology (Box 14)
    - Cell Biology (Box 14)
    - History of Science and Medicine (Box 14)
    - Other: Health Science Resources (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Anesthesiology (Box 14)
    - Dermatology (Box 14)
    - Internal Medicine (Box 14)
    - Neurology (Box 14)
    - Obstetrics and Gynecology (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Ophthalmology (Box 14)
    - Pediatrics (Box 14)
    - Psychiatry (Box 14)
    - Epidemiology and Public Health (Box 14)
    - Therapeutic Radiology (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Surgery (Box 14)
    - Laboratory Medicine (Box 14)
    - Human Genetics (Box 14)
    - Child Study Center (Box 14)
  - Organizations, Societies, Hospitals
    - Albany Medical College
      - General, 1958-1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Radio Conference Program, 1965-1976 (Box 15, Folder 2 - 3)
    - American College of Chest Physicians, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - American Medical Association (AMA)
      - Continuing Education, 1967-1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Council on Medical Education and Hospitals: Reports, 1953-1973 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges (AAMC)
      - Correspondence, 1958-1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Physician Performance Study, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission, 1958-1966 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Children's Community Center, Hamden, CT, 1949-1954 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut Academy of General Practice
      - General, 1961-1970 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Bridgeport Chapter, 1956-1970 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Hartford Chapter, 1963-1968 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Litchfield County Chapter, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Milford Chapter, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Naugatuck Valley Chapter, 1961-1965 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - New London County Chapter, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Stamford Chapter, 1957-1971 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Tolland County Chapter, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Connecticut State Medical Society
      - Clinical Congress, 1954-1963 (Box 16, Folder 20 - 22)
      - Clinical Congress, 1963-1967 (Box 17, Folder 23 - 27)
      - Committee on Cooperation with Medical Schools, undated (Box 17, Folder 28 - 29)
      - Committee on Postgraduate Education, 1954-1977 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Judicial Committee matters, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Hospitals
      - Bristol (Box 18, Folder 32)
      - Greenwich (Box 18, Folder 33)
      - Lawrence and Memorial Associated Hospitals, New London, CT, 1948-1952 (Box 18, Folder 34)
      - Meriden, 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 35)
      - Middlesex, Middletown, CT, 1948-1953 (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - New Milford Hospital, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - Seaside Sanatorium, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 38)
      - Southbury Training School, 1948-1963 (Box 18, Folder 39 - 40)
      - Springfield Chapter of the Academy of General Practice, 1955-1957 (Box 18, Folder 41)
      - Springfield Hospital, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 42)
      - Thayer Hospital, Waterville, ME, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 43)
      - Uncas-on-Thames Sanatorium Norwich, CT, 1950-1953 (Box 18, Folder 44)
      - West Haven Veterans Administration Hospital, 1962-1979 (Box 18, Folder 45)
      - Windham Community Hospital, Inc., 1950 (Box 18, Folder 46)
      - Woodruff Center, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Koch Medical Systems (Compton, Frederick L.), 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - National Board of Medical Examiners, 1960-1975 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - National Institute of Arthritis Study, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - New England Center for Continuing Education, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - New England States Medical Societies, 1963-1969 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - New Haven County Medical Association, 1971-1985 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Pahlavic University Medical School (Shiraz, Iran), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Pan American Federation of Associations of Medical Schools and Seminar on Curriculum Innovations, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Postgraduate Medical Institute, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - University Health, Department of, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Yale Medical Society, 1954-1967 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Postdoctoral Fellows
    - Correspondence, lists, reports on Postdoctoral Fellows, 1966-1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Association of Post-Doctoral Fellows report, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Study of Research in the Clinical Sciences, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Postgraduate Medical Education
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1961-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1 - 2)
    - Program (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Reports (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Yale-New Haven Medical Center
    - University Council on Medical Services, 1972-1979 (Box 22, Folder 1 - 6)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Photography, medical, 1962-1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Printed material: "Memo from the Dean's Office", 1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Television: CPTB, 1960-1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Restricted
    - Agreements and Contracts: Yale University and other hospitals, 1951-1953 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Atypical Growth, Committee on, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut Academy of General Practice: Windham County Chapter, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Development Goals (Campaign for Yale), 1973-1976 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Leave of Absence requests, 1975-1984 (Box 25, Folder 14 - 15)
    - Lung Research Center, 1970-1980 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Redlich, F.C.:.5 year summary to president, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Record Book, 1934-1950 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Records of the deputy dean, Arthur Ebbert Jr., 1917-1987; Accession 1988-A-063
  - Anatomy, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anatomy: D. Eager, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anesthesiology, 1969-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cancer Center, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cell biology, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Child Study Center, 1968-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clinical Research Centers, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Comparative medicine (formerly Lab Animal Sciences)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Mitruka, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - D. Morrow, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Olin Proposal, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Osbaldiston, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Veterinary Referral Clinic, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cytology, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dermatology, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Diagnostic radiology
    - 1972-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Section of nuclear medicine, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health
    - 1957-1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Reception for Dr. McCollum, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Horstmann dinner and reception, 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - CJ virus, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - History of science and medicine, 1968-1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Human genetics
    - 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Rappaport, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Rappaport: correspondence with outside sources, 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Internal medicine
    - 1 of 2, 1961-1971 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 2 of 2, 1971-1979 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Medical clinic, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Microbiology, 1972-1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Neurobiology, 1968-1979 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Obstetrics/gynecology
    - 1962-1979 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - LSOG and primate facility, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Ophthalmology, 1971-1979 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Ophthalmology and visual science: eye disease registry, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Oral surgery, 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Pathology
    - 1961-1979 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Pediatrics
    - 1968-1979 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Endero reception, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Pharmacology, 1969-1977 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Physical sciences, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Physiology, 1973-1979 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Psychiatry
    - 1968-1979 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Search committee, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Delgado, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Radiology
    - Faculty and Space affairs, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Review, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Therapeutic radiology, 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Surgery
    - 1956-1979 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Search committee, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Gross anatomy, 1974-1980 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Neuropathology
      - 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 62)
      - Manuelidis/Wood Kalb, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - Manuelidis/Paulak, research, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Of historical interest, 1917-1954 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Private diagnostic clinic, 1949-1961 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Dean's reception, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Fleischer portrait, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Medical center planning, statement of objectives, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Preliminary report - overall site development, Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Records of the deputy dean, 1953-1989; Accession 1990-A-059
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065.
  - Planning and Priorities Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Veteran's Administration Medical Center - Dean's Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reports of Ad Hoc Committees, 1965-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondences Association of Yale Alumni, 1979-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Medical Center / School of Medicine Correspondences, 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Medical Center / School of Medicine Correspondences, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Office of the Provost, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Medical School Council, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Medical Center Security Commission, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - University Council on Medical Affairs, 1973, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - School of Medicine Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Pathology Chairman Search, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Pathology Chairman Search, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Lecture, General Correspondence, 1972-1975, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Annual Lecture: Checklist, Invitations, Publicity, etc., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Effort Study, 1970-1971, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Reports (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Correspondences, 1971-1987 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Clinical Practice, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Departments and Sections - Establishment/Reorganization (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Federal Regulations, 1979-1982, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Foreign Student Advisor Office (formerly International Office), 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Associate Dean / Government and Committee Relations Search Committee, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Grants and Contracts Director, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - General Research Support Grant, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Grants and Contracts - Assoc. Director, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Grants: Program Director, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hospice, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Community Health Care Center Plan, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Health Manpower Legislation, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Health Insurance, 1971-1981 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Industry - University Relationships, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Associate Dean Medical Education Search Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Medical School Administration - Planning, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Medical School Administration - General, 1967-1986 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Medical Letter - CME Program, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Associate Dean - Research Affairs Search Committee, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Safety to 1984, 1972-1984 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Space to 1983, 1970-1983 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Veteran's Administration, 1968-1984 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Yale Health Plan, 1968-1981 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Pediatrics - Department Review Jan 29-30, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Development Advisory Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Strike - 1984 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Stauffer Chemical Co., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Student Summer Programs, 1966-1985 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Grants and Contracts - BRSG, 1976-1986 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - National Fund for Medical Education, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Yale School of Nursing, 1959-1974 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Publications, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Connecticut Medicine, 1970-1978 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Research - Internship, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Self-care Research Institute, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Institute of Continuing Education, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - International Health Comm., 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - International Opportunities, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Annual Lecture List to 1984, 1965-1984 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Medical Library Expansion, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Marimed, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Medical Illustrator Correspondence, 1960-1966 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Tax Matters, 1972-1985 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - University Staff Relations Group, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - USPHS - Grants, 1966-1973 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Alpha Omega Alpha, 1960-1979 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Annual Report (Title IX), 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Annual Report (Title IX), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - CFMG, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Chaplaincy, 1967-1988 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Facilities User Survey, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Federal Legislation Information, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Foreign Fellowship, 1953-1986 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Grand Jury, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Conference Center Study, 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - CT State Department of Mental Health, 1958-1967 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Pathology Contracts, 1955-1965 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Curriculum Surveys, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Meeting of 1985 Oct 31, Nov 1 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Meeting of 1985 Feb 28, Mar 1 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Meeting of 1984 Oct 22, 23 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Meeting of 1984 May 14, 15 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Meeting of 1983 Nov 17, 18 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Meeting of 1983 Apr 14, 15 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Planning and Priorities Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Meetings of 1983 Feb 24, 25 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Planning and Priorities Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Associate Dean for Clinical Affairs (Search), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Dermatology Search, 1984-1989 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Dermatology Search - Expenses, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Diagnostic Radiology Search, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Diagnostic Radiology Search, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Diagnostic Radiology, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Diagnostic Radiology Information Booklet, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Diagnostic Radiology Search - Background Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - History of Medicine Search, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Internal Medicine Search, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Internal Medicine Search - Expenses, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Internal Medicine Search Committee, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Internal Medicine Search Committee, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Chairman Search, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Working Materials and Copies, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Waxman, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Neurology Search, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - McNamara, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Neurology Search Expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - OB/GYN Chairman Search, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - OB/GYN Search - Visits, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - OB/GYN Search C. V. 's (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Department of Pediatrics, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Department of Pediatrics Briefing, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Pediatrics Search, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Pediatrics Search - Expenses, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Search Questionnaire, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Pediatric Schedules, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Pediatric Search Working Folder, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Budget / Finance, 1968-1985 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - OMB Circular A-21, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Fluid Research Grants, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 159)